var questions = {
  "qone" : {
  "level" : "ez",
  "category" : "sports",
  "question": "Which NBA coach coined the term “three-peat”?",
  "answerA" : "Pat Riley",
  "answerB" : "Phil Jackson",
  "answerC" : "Byron Scott",
  "answerD" : "Greg Popovich",
  "correct" : "answerA",
},
"questiontwo" : {
  "level" : "ez",
  "category" : "sports",
  "question" : "How many NFL teams does California have?",
  "answerA" : "1",
  "answerB" : "3",
  "answerC" : "5",
  "answerD" : "4",
  "correct" : "answerD",
},
"questionthree" : {
  "level" : "ez",
  "category" : "sports",
  "question" : "Which team won the World Cup in 2014",
  "answerA" : "Brazil",
  "answerB" : "USA",
  "answerC" : "Germany",
  "answerD" : "U.K.",
  "correct" : "answerC",
},
"questionfour" : {
  "level" : "med",
  "category" : "sports",
  "question" : "Who is Baseball's all-time hits leader with 4,256?",
  "answerA" : "Babe Ruth",
  "answerB" : "Pete Rose",
  "answerC" : "Barry Bonds",
  "answerD" : "Hank Aaron",
  "correct" : "answerB",
},
"questionfive" : {
  "level" : "med",
  "category" : "sports",
  "question" : "Which city in Ohio has the NFL hall of fame and is the site of the annual preseason \"hall of fame game\"",
  "answerA" : "Scranton",
  "answerB" : "Canton",
  "answerC" : "Cooperstown",
  "answerD" : "Cleveland",
  "correct" : "answerB",
},
"questionsix" : {
  "level" : "med",
  "category" : "sports",
  "question" : "How many championships did Michael Jordan and Phil Jackson win together on the Bulls?",
  "answerA" : "4",
  "answerB" : "5",
  "answerC" : "6",
  "answerD" : "11",
  "correct" : "answerC",
},
"questionseven" : {
  "level" : "hard",
  "category" : "sports",
  "question" : "Which NCAA Basketball coach has the most championships with 12?",
  "answerA" : "Mike Krzyzewski (Coach K)",
  "answerB" : "Bobby Knight",
  "answerC" : "John Madden",
  "answerD" : "John Wooden",
  "correct" : "answerD",
},
"questioneight" : {
  "level" : "hard",
  "category" : "sports",
  "question" : "Who has won the PGA Player of the Year Award a record setting 11 times?",
  "answerA" : "Jack Nicklaus",
  "answerB" : "Rory Mcilroy",
  "answerC" : "Arnold Palmer",
  "answerD" : "Tiger Woods",
  "correct" : "answerD",
},
"sports_hard_three" : {
  "level" : "hard",
  "category" : "sports",
  "question" : "Jules Bianchi was recently killed in a Formula One race, his death has been the first in Formula One since this movie-inspiring story of a Brazillian in 1994 featuring: ",
  "answerA" : "Mario Andretti",
  "answerB" : "Ayrton Sena",
  "answerC" : "Michael Schumaker",
  "answerD" : "Niki Lauda",
  "correct" : "answerB",
},
"sports_hard_four" : {
  "level" : "hard",
  "category" : "sports",
  "question" : "At which college did Peyton Manning play football?",
  "answerA" : "Georgia",
  "answerB" : "Florida",
  "answerC" : "USC",
  "answerD" : "Tennessee",
  "correct" : "answerD",
},
"ww2_easy_one" : {
  "level" : "ez",
  "category" : "ww2",
  "question" : "What is the name of the still visible sunken U.S. battleship that accounted for almost half the casualties at Pearl Harbor?",
  "answerA" : "U.S.S. Arizona",
  "answerB" : "U.S.S. Constitution",
  "answerC" : "U.S.S. Nevada",
  "answerD" : "U.S.S. Califonia",
  "correct" : "answerA",
},
"ww2_easy_two" : {
  "level" : "ez",
  "category" : "ww2",
  "question" : "What was the name given to the alliance between Adolph Hitler, Benito Mussolini, and Emperor Hirohito in World War II?",
  "answerA" : "Alliance of evil",
  "answerB" : "Axis of evil",
  "answerC" : "Angels of evil",
  "answerD" : "Allied Forces",
  "correct" : "answerB",
},
"ww2_easy_three" : {
  "level" : "ez",
  "category" : "ww2",
  "question" : "\"D-Day\" or \"“Operation Overlord\" occurred on the beaches of Normandy in what country?",
  "answerA" : "France",
  "answerB" : "U.K.",
  "answerC" : "Netherlands",
  "answerD" : "Germany",
  "correct" : "answerA",
},
"ww2_med_one" : {
  "level" : "med",
  "category" : "ww2",
  "question" : "Which of these World War II beligerants was estimated to have more tanks than the rest of the world combined?",
  "answerA" : "USA",
  "answerB" : "Russia",
  "answerC" : "Germany",
  "answerD" : "China",
  "correct" : "answerB",
},
"ww2_med_two" : {
  "level" : "med",
  "category" : "ww2",
  "question" : "All of these were bloody LAND battles of the Pacific Theater except:",
  "answerA" : "Guadalcanal",
  "answerB" : "Midway",
  "answerC" : "Peleliu",
  "answerD" : "Iwo Jima",
  "correct" : "answerB",
},
"ww2_med_three" : {
  "level" : "med",
  "category" : "ww2",
  "question" : "Germany's invasion or \"Anschluss\" of what country caused France and Britain to join the war?",
  "answerA" : "Poland",
  "answerB" : "Austria",
  "answerC" : "Hungary",
  "answerD" : "Czechoslovakia",
  "correct" : "answerA",
},
"ww2_med_four" : {
  "level" : "med",
  "category" : "ww2",
  "question" : "This lavish mansion on top of a mountain, often thought to be Hitler’s personal residence was actually a government meeting place:
",
  "answerA" : "Dragon's Den",
  "answerB" : "Eidelweiss Retreat",
  "answerC" : "Lion's Gate",
  "answerD" : "Eagle's Nest",
  "correct" : "answerD",
},
"ww2_hard_one" : {
  "level" : "hard",
  "category" : "ww2",
  "question" : "The invasion of the U.S.S.R. by Germany was named Operation _____:",
  "answerA" : "Market Garden",
  "answerB" : "Overlord",
  "answerC" : "Uranus",
  "answerD" : "Zauberflöte",
  "correct" : "answerB",
},
"ww2_hard_two" : {
  "level" : "hard",
  "category" : "ww2",
  "question" : " The U.S. Navy lost 4 aircraft carriers (CV Class) in 1942 (and total during the war), they were the: U.S.S. Yorktown, U.S.S. Lexington, U.S.S. Hornet and:",
  "answerA" : "U.S.S. Concord",
  "answerB" : "U.S.S. Stinger",
  "answerC" : "U.S.S. Essex",
  "answerD" : "U.S.S. Wasp",
  "correct" : "answerD",
},
"ww2_hard_three" : {
  "level" : "hard",
  "category" : "ww2",
  "question" : "This major U.S. Battle in the area now known as Benelux had 89,500 total casualties, more than Guadalcanal and Normandy combined:",
  "answerA" : "Battle of Britain",
  "answerB" : "Battle of Okinawa",
  "answerC" : "Battle of the Bulge",
  "answerD" : "Battle of Stalingrad",
  "correct" : "answerC",
},
"music_easy_one" : {
  "level" : "ez",
  "category" : "music",
  "question" : "In 2011, which female artist sold 25 million copies of her hit album \"21\"",
  "answerA" : "Taylor Swift",
  "answerB" : "Adele",
  "answerC" : "Beyonce",
  "answerD" : "Brittney Spears",
  "correct" : "answerB",
},
"music_easy_two" : {
  "level" : "ez",
  "category" : "music",
  "question" : "In 1979 Charlie Daniels released his famous track about a fiddle playing contest with the devil called the Devil went down to ____",
  "answerA" : "Florida",
  "answerB" : "Georgia",
  "answerC" : "Mississippi",
  "answerD" : "Harlem",
  "correct" : "answerB",
},
"music_easy_three" : {
  "level" : "ez",
  "category" : "music",
  "question" : " What legendary US festival that hosted over 350,000 fans took place in 1969 in New York and has had tributary events every ten years since?",
  "answerA" : "Gunstock",
  "answerB" : "The Vans Warped Tour",
  "answerC" : "Ozzfest",
  "answerD" : "Woodstock",
  "correct" : "answerD",
},
"music_med_one" : {
  "level" : "med",
  "category" : "music",
  "question" : "Who has made 3 albums that have sold 30 million or more, including an album that sold an estimated 46 million copies (the highest of all time)",
  "answerA" : "Paul McCartney",
  "answerB" : "Bob Dylan",
  "answerC" : "Michael Jackson",
  "answerD" : "Garth Brooks",
  "correct" : "answerC",
},
"music_med_two" : {
  "level" : "med",
  "category" : "music",
  "question" : "Who played bass guitar for The Beatles?",
  "answerA" : "John",
  "answerB" : "Paul",
  "answerC" : "Ringo",
  "answerD" : "George",
  "correct" : "answerA",
},
"music_med_three" : {
  "level" : "med",
  "category" : "music",
  "question" : "Which long haired musician would famously do anything for love (but he won’t do that)?",
  "answerA" : "Meat Loaf",
  "answerB" : "Bruce Springsteen",
  "answerC" : "Billy Joel",
  "answerD" : "John Lennon",
  "correct" : "answerA",
},














}
